{
    "subject": "resource/Alps_Electric",
    "predicate": "ontology/subsidiary",
    "object": "resource/Cirque_Corporation",
    "human_readable": "Alps Electric is a subsidiary of Cirque Corporation.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9835681915283203,
            "question": "Is Alps Electric a part of Cirque Corporation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9795622825622559,
            "question": "Alps Electric is a ______ of Cirque Corporation."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.910381555557251,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Alps Electric and Cirque Corporation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9073941707611084,
            "question": "Name a subsidiary of Cirque Corporation."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8143309354782104,
            "question": "What is the name of Cirque Corporation's subsidiary?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8037033081054688,
            "question": "Which company owns Alps Electric?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7510077357292175,
            "question": "What type of company is Alps Electric?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7368052005767822,
            "question": "Who owns Alps Electric?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6056650876998901,
            "question": "To which larger company does Alps Electric belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43254393339157104,
            "question": "Is Cirque Corporation a parent company?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Alps Electric is a subsidiary of Cirque Corporation.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8295_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which larger company does Alps Electric belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8295_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who owns Alps Electric?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8295_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of company is Alps Electric?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8295_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8295_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8295_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8295_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8295_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8295_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8295_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8295_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8295_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8295_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8295_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` "
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention that Cirque Corporation became a wholly owned subsidiary of Alps Electric Co., Ltd. (in 2003, referred to as Alps Alpine) and not the other way around."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents clearly state that Cirque Corporation became a wholly owned subsidiary of Alps Electric Co., Ltd. in 2003, which contradicts the given triple stating that Alps Electric is a subsidiary of Cirque Corporation."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Cirque Corporation is a subsidiary of ALPS Electric, not the other way around.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several pieces of text state that Cirque Corporation is a subsidiary of Alps Electric, not the other way around.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context clearly states that Cirque Corporation became a wholly owned subsidiary of Alps Electric Co., Ltd. in 2003, not the other way around.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}